Finding Aid for Michigan Citizens for Humphrey and Muskie records, 1968
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Michigan Citizens for Humphrey and Muskie records 1968
Michigan Citizens for Humphrey and Muskie.
0.3 linear feet
85279 Bt 2
Political organization supporting the Democratic ticket for President in 1968. Correspondence and financial records concerning the campaign; also papers and photographs concerning the pre-convention campaign for the nomination of Hubert Humphrey for President.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group was received from Congressman James O’Hara (donor no. 5939 ).
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
The organization was established in the summer of 1968 to support the candidacy of Hubert Humphrey for Democratic nomination for President of the United States. The organization was originally named Michigan Citizens for Humphrey. With Humphrey's nomination, the organization became Michigan Citizens for Humphrey and Muskie.
The record group consists of correspondence, memoranda, organizational papers, a financial report, and delegate material from the Democratic National Convention. There is, in addition, a folder of campaign photos and a reel-to-reel tape of a campaign message.
Subjects:
Democratic Party (Mich.).; Humphrey, Hubert H. (Hubert Horatio), 1911-1978.; Michigan Citizens for Humphrey and Muskie.; Michigan--Politics and government--1961-1970.; Muskie, Edmund S., 1914-; Presidents--United States--Election--1968.; United States--Politics and government--1963-1969.; Michigan--Politics and government--1951-
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Humphrey, Hubert H. (Hubert Horatio), 1911-1978.; Political elections--1968.; Politics and government--1961-1970.
Subjects - Sound Recordings:
Michigan Citizens for Humphrey and Muskie.; Presidents--United States--Election--1968.; Michigan--Politics and government--1961-1970.; Michigan--Politics and government--1951-
Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Sound recordings.
- Organizational records
  - Operational certificates and applications (Box 1)
  - Financial report, November 26, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Employees Time book (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, mailings, etc.
    - Undated (Box 1)
    - April-May 1968 (Box 1)
    - June 1968 (Box 1)
    - July 1968 (Box 1)
    - August 1968 (Box 1)
    - September 1968 (Box 1)
    - October 1968 (Box 1)
    - November 1968 (Box 1)
  - Michigan National Convention Delegates, 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Photographs of Hubert Humphrey campaigning in Michigan. (Box 1)
  - Sound recording: political message sponsored during the 1968 presidential campaign, (7 1/2 ips ;5 in. (Box 1)